[Jinman panting]
[J] Long time no see, Jeong Jinman.
[Jinman grunting]
[♪ tense music playing]
[Jinman and J grunting]
[J choking, gurgling]
[knife slashing]
Q,
unfortunately, the operation
that you've all been a part of
will be temporarily suspended.
[Marco] Suspended?
What are you talking about?
Even after losing J and X?
Then…
what about Jeong Jinman?
[Jin] It's an order from the higher-ups.
Securing the server is our priority.
Babylon doesn't care if Jinman dies.
[scoffs]
Priority?
It's best if you go back to Japan.
[Jin] We need to send J back home as well.
[♪ eerie tense music playing]
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 05
NEGOTIATION
[Jian] Woojin, hey!
Don't close your eyes! No, you can't!
-[muffled gunfire]
-[breathing heavily]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[birds chirping]
[knocking on door]
[nurse] Miss Arin? You're awake now.
I'm not Miss Arin.
What?
It's Jian.
Jeong Jian.
[nurse] Uh…
The doctor on duty will be here
in 30 minutes.
Uh, please don't get up, Jian.
STYLE
::cue()
[Jaewon] This is your new ID.
-We've created a new identity for you.
-What about my uncle?
I'm pretty sure he was in my room earlier.
You're right.
He was here a few minutes before you woke.
But he had to take care of something,
so he left.
SOCIAL SECURITY CARD
LEE YENA
I don't need the ID card.
Changing identities is
kind of useless anyway.
I'll just stay Jeong Jian.
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
[Jaewon] I know you're still processing,
but we've put together
a statement for you.
The boat had been docked at the pier.
Then Mr. Woojin brought you along
for the maintenance and inspection.
We were out at sea
when the boat broke down.
The reef punctured the boat.
The ship started sinking
because water rushed in.
I put on the life jacket
that was on board.
But Woojin…
thought he could save us
by fixing the engine.
His leg got caught
in the damaged wheelhouse.
He was dragged down with the boat.
I lost… consciousness.
I woke up in the hospital.
All right, that's all for now.
You can go, you must be exhausted.
[sighs] Poor Woojin.
I can't believe this happened.
[in Japanese] It's fortunate that it was
successful there in Thailand at least.
For now, take the recovered items and…
[door opening]
[door closes]
Take the recovered item
and return to Korea.
[call-ending beep]
Honestly, people in this country
have no basic manners.
[in English] What's going on?
Uh…
It's, uh…
Black Mountain Alliance has received
organized support for years
from a private military company
named Babylon.
Clashes between militant
factions are now spreading
into neighboring regions.
-Authorities are treating…
-That's not, uh…
That's not all.
The assassinations of the high-ranking
government officials have escalated.
According to sources,
there is a possibility
that this was a strategic operation.
The evidence is leading
to a private organization--
[reporter] We are joined today
by an expert in the field.
The weapons North Korea unveiled
at the Victory Day parade
have been significantly upgraded.
Jeong Jinman.
That disgusting parasite.
STYLE
::cue()
[indistinct chatter]
[♪ somber music playing]
[Jeomrye] Arin.
Arin…
are you blaming yourself?
[sobs softly]
Most of the aunties here
have lost their husbands
because something
happened to them out at sea.
They see it as their fate.
It's life.
I'm sorry.
[sobbing]
Auntie, really, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Auntie.
So sorry.
[♪ somber music continues]
Listen well.
You're blaming yourself,
but it won't bring Woojin back.
You need to keep living your own life.
Understand?
I know it's hard right now,
but when you look back,
you'll see that
this is just a moment in your life.
You must be brave.
Make sure to live tenaciously and be bold.
You'll heal Arin by living a good life.
[continues sobbing]
We're all right.
Don't worry about us here.
Just live.
Arin, go.
Forget about us.
Live your life.
[L] You'll be all right alone?
We'll come back tomorrow.
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ tense somber music playing]
Now…
I'm all alone.
[Q crying]
[♪ music slowly turns foreboding]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs, sniffles]
[Q] Jeong Jinman…
this is the darkness you created.
I will make you pay for it.
[♪ music crescendos]
[♪ music ends]
You and your brother,
you've always been good kids.
From when he was this tall
and you were this tall.
I'm in your debt.
Sir, thank you for the past few days.
Ichika…
reach out to me anytime you need.
I appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Be strong.
[♪ tense pensive music playing]
Is M still in Thailand?
He's back in Korea with the asset.
-He apologized for not being here.
-Yeah.
Thank you for being here.
So what now?
Let's go back to Korea.
I'm going to murder Jeong Jinman
with my own hands.
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ tense music playing]
[worker] Hey, you're gonna
have to wait, okay?
[indistinct chatter]
[worker] Thank you. Thank you so much.
[mouse clicks]
[door opening]
[security camera whirs]
[door closes]
Boss, a lot of orders
from the Philippines are coming in.
Hm?
Oh!
Jeong Jian!
[♪ soft music playing]
[Jian] When did you move in?
Uh… We've been preparing this whole time,
but it's only been about ten days
since we settled in.
[lock clicks]
[digital trills]
[lock beeping, clicking]
[thuds]
I'll carry it.
-I've got it.
-Okay.
[mechanical whirring]
[thuds]
I'm really glad that
you didn't get hurt, Jeong Jian.
Jeong Jinman is… here, right?
Mm-hmm. The boss was really
worried about you.
[♪ pensive music playing]
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[bag thuds]
[Jian] You're okay, right?
[sighs in relief]
So glad you're here.
[♪ soft tense music playing]
[mechanical whirring]
[thuds]
This will be your room for the time being.
Oh, great. No windows for me.
Yeah. Obviously. It's a basement.
Take some time to rest.
You're probably exhausted.
I tried to decorate it like our old place.
It reminds me of that day.
It's not exactly the same, right?
No cameras in my room this time?
You made the right choice.
Thanks for coming back, Jeong Jian.
I didn't come back to make you happy.
[sighs]
You scared me.
You should stop.
Boss, I said, we shouldn't put
a camera in there.
Wait a sec.
That camera was already installed there.
You decided to make that Jian's room.
That's not important.
Don't think about continuing
to spy on her.
-Hey. Look. Do me a favor.
-Huh?
Get rid of it before she notices.
-This guy…
-[sighs] Thanks.
[inhales deeply]
[cries softly]
[♪ soft somber music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[phone buzzing]
[Babylon executive 1] This information
leak cost about 20 billion dollars.
What will happen if they find out
we supplied the weapons
to both the government and the rebels?
[sighs irritably]
The rebels aren't the problem right now.
What do you think North Korea would do?
The US government won't just sit back
and do nothing.
The Korean branch dropped the ball.
I'm here to recover it.
[Babylon executive 2] Nonsense!
Take some responsibility!
[Chen] However…
didn't this highly confidential
information become public
because your operation failed?
The operation failure
was entirely my responsibility.
Good job, everyone.
I'll take it from here.
[Chen] You were careless
and moved impulsively.
Did you stop to think about
what will happen
if Jeong Jinman decides to leak
other confidential information?
I apologize for my actions.
Do you think that I can't see through you?
Your self-interest is clear.
You're planning to use the murthehelp app
to conduct your own business, are you not?
I'm not, sir. I only have
Babylon's best interests in mind.
I understand. I've read the report too.
I get that it's
a very attractive business model.
But that should not be our first priority.
Correct?
We have no interest
in that cockroach Jeong Jinman.
Whether you decide to kill him
or buy him, do what you please.
We need you to prioritize.
You are to retrieve the server first.
Your message is received.
[Chen] Regarding the murthehelp system,
I will leave it to your discretion
on how to take over and move forward
with the business.
If you are successful, I will entrust
the entirety of Babylon Korea to you.
[♪ tense music playing]
[Minhye] She's staying in a hotel
that's not very far from Babylon.
[Jinwoo] Since it's just a regular hotel,
it should be fairly easy to gain access.
[Minhye] I guarantee
it won't be as easy as you think.
[guide, in Chinese]
We will have breakfast together.
And depart at eight o'clock sharp tomorrow
to begin our sightseeing schedule.
Depart at eight o'clock. Understood!
That's all for today's schedule
and you can rest in your rooms.
[camera shutters click rapidly]
[guide] The convenience store is
on the first floor
and you can use it freely, anytime.
[elevator chimes]
[in English] Why are you up here?
[in Chinese] Huh? Where's everybody?
Strange. Did I get off on the wrong floor?
[in English] This floor is fully booked
for conference participants only.
[Minhye, in Chinese] Really?
[bodyguard, in English] I'm sorry?
[in Chinese] It's nothing. Nothing.
I didn't understand.
Oh, it's okay.
Wow, but you're really tall, aren't you?
[in English] What's going on?
A Chinese tourist came up here by mistake.
[Minhye] It looks like that woman
and her little sidekick
are staying on the same floor.
Should I eliminate them when I can?
I can probably do it pretty easily.
No, thanks.
Even if you eliminate them, Babylon will
just keep sending their replacements.
Do you know her?
When I was in the special forces,
we had an operation to rescue hostages
in Southeast Asia.
That's the only time we've met.
There were Koreans
amongst the Japanese hostages.
STYLE
::cue()
Since Japan couldn't deploy troops,
Babylon was called in.
You said, in Hanam-do,
the Babylon team leader was
a Japanese woman, right?
If memory serves correct,
her code name is Q.
[♪ soft pensive music playing]
[sighs]
Cheolseung,
look into the team leader and Q,
and include all of their team members
that entered Korea.
Get all the detailed information you can.
[Q] I'm Q.
The next time we meet,
we'll go have a drink together.
[in Japanese] Thank you.
[in English]
Long time no see, Jeong Jinman.
[phone buzzing]
ATTORNEY JANG INSEOP
[Cheolseung]
"Negotiation requested." [scoffs]
Those dumb assholes always have
to fuck around and find out the hard way.
[Jinwoo] We can't do this now.
We don't have enough manpower.
Code Yellow took heavy losses
on Hanam-do Island.
Our Code Reds are scattered.
They're waiting to see what happens.
Right, it could be dangerous.
It's not time to negotiate.
Let's secure a safe house first.
And then we can move Jian.
[Jian] Am I some kind of object?
Move me wherever you want?
Over and over.
Without ever negotiating.
You hide, then fight and move.
You repeat the cycle again and again.
And then what?
How many people are gonna die
to protect me?
Do you even know
how many people on Hanam-do Island died?
[scoffs]
When Uncle Jinwoo dies
and Minhye Eonni dies, does this end?
I won't accept that.
I'm not allowing any of you
to sacrifice yourselves.
Do you understand?
That's why I came back.
All right. What's your plan, then?
What are you going to do
to prevent all of us…
from being sacrificed?
Whatever I can.
[scoffs]
Listen up, Jeong Jian.
It's not possible to negotiate
without strength.
You can't just talk a big game.
You better put your money
where your mouth is first.
You need to prove it.
Hm.
I get it.
I'll prove it to you.
Tell me what to do, I'll do it.
[rain pouring]
[♪ tense music playing]
[voicemail] The customer you have dialed
cannot answer your call.
Please hang up and try the call again.
[Jian] No umbrella?
I forgot my umbrella all the time
when I was little.
[chuckles softly]
See this? Do you want one?
Try them on.
It's all right. You can trust me.
I'm friends with your father.
[chuckles softly]
[Jian] What?
-[Jian] Oh, no.
-[child] Why are you so bad at this?
[Jian] Why are you so good at this?
-You--
-[child] Shoot!
[car horn honking]
Oh, hey. It's my dad.
-General Suho!
-Hi, Dad!
Where did you get this raincoat?
Your friend. She gave me an extra one.
STYLE
::cue()
Hm? My friend?
Mr. Lee Jaeyoon. It's good to see you.
Oh, it's been a while.
Good to see you too. Hey.
Suho, jump in the car, wait for Dad.
[Suho] Thank you for the raincoat.
See you later.
[Jian] Bye.
[thunder rumbling]
[Jian groans]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What do you want? Why are you here?
-[strained] Jeong Jian.
-Speak louder.
[strained]
I'm Jeong Jian, Jeong Jinman's niece.
Jeong Jian? Code Green?
[Jian grunts, coughs]
Did Jinman send you?
That guy's a total scumbag.
He sent you after my son?
It's pretty funny hearing
the word scumbag…
-come out of your mouth.
-What?
[sighs]
The day Mr. Kim betrayed us
and brought all the Code Reds to attack.
Why weren't you there?
[scoffs]
Did Jinman send you
to confront me about this?
No.
I didn't come here
to argue with you, all right?
I'm here for a reason.
Only two people on this Earth can persuade
the Code Reds to move.
My uncle said one of them was Mr. Kim,
but he's dead.
That's why I'm here.
The only other person is you,
Mr. Ahn Seongbeom.
-Will you please persuade the Code Reds?
-Maybe you haven't heard.
[Seongbeom] I'm retired.
[Jian] Wait.
Aren't you even curious?
I found your son.
I knew who you were…
and what your alias was.
You know what's cool?
I offered the Code Purples extra money
to give me info on you, but they declined.
They said it's an unwritten rule.
Never touch family.
Every one of them refused to say anything.
So how do you think it is
that I found out who you were…
and exactly where your son was?
Babylon's been collecting
personal information on every Code Red.
Those assholes put every single one
of you under surveillance.
[angrily] Why?
Tell me why!
I'm retired!
Why is Babylon digging up my information?
Why do you think, huh?
It's always about money.
Babylon is a big corporation
and they're trying to swallow murthehelp,
to take over.
I'll be blunt with you.
The Babylon division from Japan
came to take murthehelp from us.
They've been trying to mobilize Code Reds.
They've even created a fake app
and are recruiting people without codes.
They'll probably start a war with us.
We don't have enough manpower.
We need your help.
Jeong Jinman, you listening?
Your niece has guts.
But if you ever try to send anyone
to my son again,
I promise you,
I'll have no problems tearing apart
and killing both you and your niece.
The only reason I'm holding back now
is as a final courtesy to you
as an old colleague of mine.
[♪ tense pensive music playing]
[Jian sighs]
[Jian] I think I messed it up.
Please come and get me.
STYLE
::cue()
You won't be able to change
Ahn Seongbeom's mind that easily.
Don't give up yet.
I didn't go to see his son
to threaten his family.
[sighs]
It just backfired.
Jian…
you probably feel that
your uncle really messed up your life
by involving you in all of this.
But he really does care.
And trust me, he understands
the pain of losing someone you love.
Jinman's lost a lot of people
in every stage of his life.
As a soldier, a mercenary,
and long after leaving Babylon.
It's been hard.
Jinman's experienced so much loss that…
at some point he just accepted
this endless cycle of pain.
That's why he's so guarded with everyone.
Your uncle wanted you
to be strong and resilient.
He just doesn't want you
to end up like he did.
I don't want to end up like him either.
I'm not going to do things like he did.
Ever.
I heard that you want to spar with me.
Since Master Pasin's not here--
[groans]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Inventory check is the basics
of running the shopping mall.
Finish all of this today
and make sure you get it inspected.
[Minhye grunts]
[Jian grunts]
[Jinwoo] This is 9 mm.
This is 5.56,
and this is 7.62.
Simply put, the larger the caliber,
the more damage it does.
[gunshots]
[Minhye] A longer barrel
increases the range.
When the sun's in front of you,
close the scope cover
and look in the middle.
Or you'll give yourself away
because of the sun's reflection.
You can ask Brother
to give you a few of these.
[gunshot]
In order to prepare for hacker attacks,
we maintain our security by switching
the site cover every 72 hours.
Click the invisible button
under the event tag
and it'll reveal the login
to the real site.
When you log in
using the three biometric credentials
that you originally registered with,
along with the code,
you will get access
to the real murthehelp.
What'd you do? Why'd you get denied?
Poor circulation.
[♪ upbeat music continues]
[Jian and Minhye grunting]
STYLE
::cue()
No!
[panting]
You already finished dismantling it?
This clover protected my life
when I escaped North Korea.
It's yours now.
You're giving it to me?
My wishes all came true already.
I don't need it anymore.
[Jian] Thank you, as always, Director Kim.
Let's begin the new company agreement
between Jaewon Co. Ltd. and murthehelp.
[gunfire]
-[♪ music ends]
-This way, hurry.
[shushes]
This place is a place only the boss
and I know about.
Jeong Jian, listen well.
This place is a secret passage
you can use to escape in an emergency.
You have to go in about 300 meters.
When you reach the 250-meter mark,
you can slam
the blast door shut behind you.
What's at the end of it?
The exit?
Oh, right. In front of it,
there's a small room.
Like the old shopping mall.
From there, you can just…
[mimics fire whooshing]
burn the whole shopping mall down.
-Why?
You're escaping through means
that it's an emergency situation
and you can't leave any traces behind.
[♪ eerie music playing]
[Jian panting]
[Jian] Eonni.
Do you think it's gonna be hard for me
to live a normal life like everybody else?
[Minhye] Jinman…
am I going to have a hard time living
a normal life like everyone else?
-[gunshot echoing]
-[people screaming]
[♪ somber music playing]
[in Chinese] You fucking bitch.
Who on Earth are you?
[Minhye] You don't remember?
I am the fucking bitch
that you sold for 100 dollars.
-[gunshot ringing]
-[bullet casing clattering]
[Jinman, in English] Yeah.
Probably.
You won't be able
to live like everyone else.
STYLE
::cue()
It's not possible, Jian.
But… luckily,
your uncle is still alive and well.
And there are people
who want to protect you.
We eat meals together,
spend time together.
Like you're doing with me right now.
Maybe…
this is our own kind of normal.
[grunts]
[Jian grunts, groans]
-[Jian] What is this?
-What do you mean, what is this?
The enemy will take advantage
of your weakness.
You gotta keep your head together.
[grunts]
[exhales sharply]
What?
What are you doing here at this hour?
Jian told me to come.
She called a meeting.
What?
Huh?
[♪ tense music playing]
Everyone is here.
I gave things some serious thought.
This man.
-[Jin] The server administrator?
-[K] Yes.
One of the prior administrators
happened to be on the bus
that we ordered to be exploded.
-So we hired a new one.
-Okay.
-You vetted him thoroughly, right?
-Yes.
Who was that man?
Head of security
during Lee Yonghan's time here.
Oh…
He let Jeong Jinman get away,
lost the server, and yet here he is.
[K] I'll take care of it.
What is it now?
Negotiate?
They made the offer first?
[in Korean] Yes. No.
[in English] Yes.
[Jin exhales deeply]
What are you playing at, Jeong Jinman?
So where are we doing this?
STYLE
::cue()
[truck rumbling]
[♪ tense music playing]
[truck door clanks]
Where is Jeong Jinman?
Jeong Jinman's not coming.
[♪ tense music continues]
I'm Jeong Jian.
I will be doing the negotiating.
You're breaking your promise again.
Do you think we're playing
some kind of game here?
You are the one…
playing games.
[screams] Aren't you, Ms. Kusanagi?
The CEO came in person on our side.
It's uneven.
The status level should match
in negotiation, but there is…
a proxy instead of you.
[doors whirring]
[♪ sinister music playing]
[Q] This is your last chance.
If you don't come with me,
your boyfriend will also die.
[heartbeat thumps rapidly]
STYLE
::cue()
[scoffs]
You two have met before.
You remember, don't you?
In order to match my status level,
Jeong Jinman would need to be
the one sitting in front of me.
But it's fine.
You and I are lucky
to live in today's world,
a world where a young lady like you
can become a CEO.
Like me.
[♪ suspenseful tense music playing]
Ms. Kusanagi, I apologize
for the damage caused to Babylon
over the past two years.
[laughs]
I'll accept that.
I'd hardly call that damage, though.
It doesn't even scratch the surface
compared to what you've been through.
You lost your parents when you were seven
and found out what your uncle really did
for a living when you became an adult.
Not to mention the day you survived
the carnage in your home.
Do you remember when you shot the drone
with your slingshot?
-[Jin chuckles]
-Hm.
We were expecting to meet with Jinman.
Our intention was to hold him responsible
for Babylon's losses.
But his niece showed up instead.
That's too bad.
Well, I'm the one here.
You're going to have to negotiate with me.
Oh, yeah? Why would we do that?
Starting this very minute,
Jeong Jinman is no longer involved
with murthehelp.
He's officially stepped down.
This vicious cycle of fighting
will keep repeating
as long as Jeong Jinman is involved.
The problem is that his style of operation
always uses force with force.
If the fighting never stops…
both sides will continue to lose.
I want us to coexist together.
I'm proposing we form a partnership.
Murthehelp and Babylon working together.
As we hand over the server,
we'll also be sharing
murthehelp's business with Babylon.
You can stop…
[clears throat]
No need to bother making knock-offs,
like that half-baked app you made.
Instead, we'll share the profits
and prioritize Babylon's weapons
in our Sales and Distribution departments.
Also, if over time,
we feel that there's enough trust
built between us,
we might even be open to the possibility
of selling murthehelp entirely to Babylon
at a reasonable price.
M and A.
That sound good?
[server admin, in Japanese]
He says they haven't breached anything
other than the exposed data.
They've only breached the exposed data.
And your terms?
[♪ suspenseful tense music continues]
They're simple.
Jeong Jinman.
Nobody's allowed to touch him from now on.
In other words, you are asking us
to spare your uncle's life.
In so many words.
This is the key to the truck.
If you pick it up, I'll consider it
as you accepting my offer.
You're very bold
in begging for Jinman's life.
If you brought me ten of Jinman's heads
wrapped in a tiny little bow,
STYLE
::cue()
it still wouldn't be enough.
If I refuse?
Then…
we'll all…
die right here.
-[alarm blares]
-[guns clicking]
See those bombs?
They're linked to my biometric signal.
The moment that signal's cut…
[slams table]
…they'll detonate.
Maybe it's because you're young,
you're not afraid of dying.
You're so reckless.
Dying?
I don't care about that anymore.
I'm beyond that now.
I already died once on that island.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Are you scared?
Let's hear it.
Is dying…
something you're afraid of?
Lights!
[Seongbeom] Switch to infrared now.
I've long wondered
how you survived
those impossible situations.
Seeing you now, I finally understand.
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
See you soon, Jeong Jian.
[exhales]
[exhales sharply]
-I appreciate it.
-Fuck that bullshit.
Jeong Jinman,
I didn't come because I like you.
I broke my promise to your niece
that one day.
But now I've paid my debt.
I'm done with murthehelp and code shit
and anything related to it.
-Forget about me.
-I appreciate it, regardless.
Let's go.
[♪ gentle music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[Cheolseung]
When you shouted "Ms. Kusanagi,"
you scared the living hell out of me.
[Jian] When did I do that?
[Cheolseung] Little Jian was so cool.
[Minhye] She really has
grown into herself.
[Cheolseung] Hey, how did you know
it was a camera?
-I just looked and saw it.
-Oh, your bloodline is strong.
[chuckles] Hurry up and eat. It's done.
[Brother] Don't eat it all!
Leave me some too!
[Jinwoo] Oh, man, our Brother is
a samgyeopsal killer. What a shame!
[Cheolseung] Hey, just
stuff your face with ramyeon.
-Challenge!
-[Jian] Finish up there and come down.
They're rubbing it in.
-Code Blue?
-Transport is really important.
We have to deliver the products
to the target locations discreetly,
but right now
each code handles them directly.
By creating a new code
that specializes in transportation,
I think it would really help us
down the line, don't you?
What do you think?
Why look at me?
Murthehelp's CEO is Jeong Jian.
If she says we should do it,
then we do it.
Okay. Good.
I'm Code Blue number one.
I always fly the helicopter
or drive the car.
-I handle all transportation, right?
-[Jian] No.
-Uncle Jinwoo, you can't be Code Blue.
-Why not?
One more thing.
I would like if all of us here…
Brother included.
Everybody at this table,
becomes Code Green from now on.
What?
It's only natural. You're all important.
We've all become like family now.
It's only right that you're Code Green.
That means that Uncle Jinwoo,
you're not Code Blue. You're Code Green.
Minhye Eonni.
Uncle Cheolseung, you too.
[♪ gentle music playing]
[Jinman clears throat]
This suddenly…
reminds me of my mother
that I had to leave behind in North Korea.
I haven't heard that word
since coming to the South.
Family.
Thank you, Jian.
Hey, come on. Let's drink to that.
Yeah? Huh?
-[Jinwoo] Okay. In one shot!
-[Jinman] Here.
Our hearts to the motherland,
our livers to our comrades.
-[Cheolseung] Cheers!
-[Jinwoo] Cans up.
[all] Cheers.
[all exhaling sharply]
[Cheolseung] If we don't celebrate on
a day like today, when will we ever, huh?
[Jinwoo] You're right. That's right. Wow!
Comrade's saying
all the right things today.
-[Jinwoo] Hey, take a photo.
-[Cheolseung] Yeah, good idea.
[camera shutter clicks]
Pasin.
[Pasin weakly] Help me, Jinman.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
[Jin] Jeong Jian…
That little kid was cute.
She must have thought
I really went to negotiate.
-[blows landing]
-[Pasin groaning, coughing]
So, in return, you are going to have
to do a little work for us.
[screams]
[♪ closing theme music playing]
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG